[logo buzzes]
[dark, unsettling
music building]
[woman]: I'm not safe in here.
I feel like I'm being watched.
Like...
...there's eyes on me.
I'm so scared.
[video glitches]
[unintelligible audio]
[thunderous bang]
[people struggling and arguing]
[arguing calms]
[footsteps thumping]
[door creaks open]
[footsteps thump]
[Riley]: Mia!
[wild animals howling]
[ominous growl]
[gloomy music plays]
[Reporter]: The hosts of
the popular YouTube channel
"Paranormal Paranoids" have now
been missing for a week.
[Reporter 2]: Speculation
abounds for the whereabouts
of the so-called
"Paranormal Paranoids."
Peter Bailey, Laura Tucker,
David Reynolds,
and Riley Brennan.
[Reporter 3]: They were last
week near the southern edge
of Darke County, Ohio,
near an abandoned town
called Shelby Oaks.
[Reporter 4]: The Darke County
Police Department say
they're doing their best
to locate them,
but have very few leads.
- These people are fakers, man.
They've always been frauds.
They're still frauds.
- They're baiting you.
Just building anticipation
for the next episode.
- They recently started
using two cameras.
The cops have one.
So, where's the other?
- The parents are requesting
that the public take
this seriously.
- This isn't a hoax.
- It's been one full week
since we learned
of their disappearance,
without a new development
in the case,
their friends and family
are starting to fear
the worst.
[picture rustles]
[Mia]: This is Riley,
as you know her,
host of "Paranormal Paranoids."
This is Riley as I know her,
my little sister.
My name is Mia Walker.
I've been searching for Riley
for the last 12 years,
and I'd like you to get to know
her the way that I do.
♪ I'm haunted in the morning
[Riley]: One, two,
three, four...
[Mia]: When we were kids,
she was very mature for her age.
She was always thinking,
figuring things out,
seeing things no one else saw.
Some people keep
a dream journal.
Riley kept a dream sketchbook.
She'd start drawing instantly,
as soon as she woke up.
She had extremely vivid dreams.
And sometimes...
she even drew her nightmares.
[Riley strumming
guitar continues]
♪ I wonder where I'm falling
[Mia]: In high school,
she started to take the arts
more seriously.
And the Riley that
I knew just melted away
when she was performing.
She really came out
of her shell.
And she got good at that.
Pretending that she was okay
when she wasn't.
♪ Big sister,
won't you find me ♪
[Mia]: So, with that passion
of hers,
it was no surprise
when the channel took off.
[mysterious music plays]
[Jess]: For the last half
of the 20th century,
UFO researchers,
demonologists, psychics,
all that, there was
a mysticism to it.
Even the idea of investigating
the supernatural
was becoming a joke.
What happened with
the Paranoids changed that.
- Since then, locals refer
to it simply as
"The Suicide Shed".
[Jess]: YouTube was brand new.
Nobody knew what it could be,
or who might be watching.
The Paranoids tapped
into an audience
that had been relegated
to UFO conventions,
and paranormal chatrooms,
and those people were starved
for content.
[Mia]: Nearly every time
they filmed,
they captured something
most paranormal researchers
spend their entire lives
looking for,
which is why they had
so many doubters.
[ominous music plays]
[Mia]: You know, at first,
I thought they could have been
faking things, sure.
I mean, I didn't know how
else to explain it.
But I also knew that Riley
wouldn't do something like that.
She took all this stuff
very seriously.
[startling bang]
[screaming]
- What was that?
[Laura]: Riley, don't go
all by yourself, Riley.
[Paranoids speaking
indistinctly]
[Laura]: Chill, chill.
[Riley]: Where did
that come from?
[door opens]
[evil growl]
[Paranoids screaming]
- Whoa! Whoa!
- Holy shit!
- I believe
my sister's not a liar.
I tried talking to her about it
but after the prison episode,
she got real quiet.
[footsteps echoing]
- Jesus.
[David]: What?
[breathing nervously]
- Don't you feel that?
[David]: No. Feel what?
- Cold.
[Laura]: Holy shit.
[David]: Oh, fuck!
[Laura]: Riley.
- What? What?
- No, it's fine.
[panicked breathing]
- Wait!
- No, Riley!
Riley!
[Peter]: Riley, no!
- We have to go now!
[ominous music peaks]
[Mia]: A lot of people called
bullshit on that.
But then the uploads stopped
and the channel went dark.
Some of the fans were worried,
but most seemed to think it
was a publicity stunt.
And then... everything changed.
- Today's top story, the hosts
of the YouTube channel,
the "Paranormal Paranoids"
have been missing for five days.
[Mia]: People started taking it
seriously after that.
It's sad to say,
but that's really where
their fame began.
After their disappearance,
people all over the world
started scouring through
their videos
searching for answers.
[Fan 1]: There are videos
of her on her channel
talking to someone
offscreen that we've never met.
The police need to be
checking everything.
[Fan 2]: Having clear sight
of a car belonging to a member
of the group may also be helpful
for us going forward,
if we ever need to identify
a vehicle.
[Fan 3]: There were plenty
of theories,
but nothing concrete
ever came forward.
- So, there is a lot
to unpack here.
- And then,
there's this odd clip
of her talking to another
Paranormal Paranoid, Peter.
[mouse clicking]
- Well, we had the gas station
security feed,
and their card numbers.
They had made their last
recorded purchase
there just outside
of Shelby Oaks.
So, we knew they at least
got that far.
Anywhere they kids might
have been going,
we had to investigate.
So, the most obvious place
was the old amusement park.
[people screaming]
[Mia]: It's about
60 miles from here.
My mom used to talk about
it all the time.
She loved going there
when she was a kid.
They had a ballroom and
bands played there.
It was pretty much the reason
to go to Shelby Oaks.
[Ferris wheel clicking]
[Mia]: The park closed
in the late 90s
after a really bad fire.
A lot of people think
the place is haunted.
[Burke]: Shelby Oaks has been
a ghost town since the late 90s.
From the perspective
of these kids, though,
I mean, that place
was a gold mine.
It seemed promising but
it was just another dead end.
- I know this is hard
for people to hear,
but I don't think these are just
going to turn up anything.
I think the energy is better
spent on finding who did it.
[Burke]: Every good cop
knows that feeling.
When it starts to sink in that
the person you're searching for
isn't coming home.
[Mia]: Robert and I met two
years before Riley went missing.
I always wanted to be a mother
and Robert always wanted
to be a daddy.
And we tried for a bit but...
it didn't happen.
And then...
when Riley went missing,
it just...
...it just wasn't the time
anymore.
Not after that.
[phone ringing]
[worrying music plays]
[Reporter]: Tragically,
the bodies of Peter Bailey,
Laura Tucker,
and David Reynolds
were found in a cabin just
outside of Shelby Oaks, Ohio,
an abandoned ghost town
the young adults
may have been investigating
for their show,
"Paranormal Paranoids."
On the front door
of the cabin,
this disturbing symbol,
smeared in blood.
Riley Brennan,
the host of the program,
is still missing.
- I'm so scared.
[Reporter]: A video camera
was discovered from the scene
that police say may have
captured the perpetrator.
[sinister music]
[Mia]: Once the footage got out,
it sparked a nationwide
campaign.
I mean, you couldn't go
to the grocery store
without seeing it
on a sign or a billboard.
- Who took Riley Brennan?
[Burke]: From the video,
we could ascertain
that the suspect was
a white male, 6'1", maybe 6'2"
based on the height
of the window.
He was wearing gloves.
So, basically we had nothing.
And...
there was uh...
there was that other thing.
We must've watched
that tape 500 times
before releasing it
to the public.
None of us saw it.
But now, like...
can't get it outta my head.
[door creaks open]
[footsteps thudding on stairs]
[loud crash]
[Riley]: Oh, God.
[sinister music plays]
[Riley]: Did I ever tell you
about the night terrors
I used to have?
I'd see this man
in my window and...
I just feel trapped.
It's-it's, I mean,
it's weird, it's crazy.
- No, no, you're fine.
- But like, I saw...
like, images of...
like, the school,
and the prison,
and these numbers.
And--
- Wait, after the fact,
or before?
- No, like, when I was 13.
[Mia]: Riley always
had a connection.
When she was little,
she had these awful
night terrors.
Like, we'd hear her screaming
and Mom and I would run into
her room and find her sweating
like she'd just run 10 miles.
I'll never forget the way
her eyes looked.
She kept saying
she saw a man
standing in her window
starting at her.
Her second story window.
We never found anything except
a crack in the glass.
She must have been 13
before she finally grew out
of that.
The last night I saw her,
she had that same look
in her eyes again,
like she knew something
was wrong.
[video glitches]
[intelligible audio]
[Mia]: There's been a lot of
debate about what she said.
I've watched it
a thousand times.
I'm positive she said,
"Mia, he's back."
[sinister music plays briefly]
When we were little,
Mom always made sure
we could find our way home.
In the woods outside,
she carved our initials
in the trees.
If we ever got lost out there,
we could just follow
the markings,
and they always led us home.
[tender music plays]
I just want to lead Riley home.
[camera woman]: Okay.
That's great.
Uh, let's take a break.
[plant litter
crunching under foot]
[crew member exhales]
- Oh, just--
[knock at door]
- Sorry.
Are you...
do you need help?
[sobbing]
- She...
she finally let me go.
[gunshot cracks]
[camera woman screams]
[police radio chatter]
[sirens wailing]
[dark, disturbing music]
[music intensifies]
[indistinct chatter]
[gunshot echoes]
[inaudible screaming]
[sinister music continues]
[music softens eerily]
[ambulance doors clunk closed]
[music peaks then fades]
[Robert]: You okay?
[Mia]: Yeah.
[footsteps thud away]
[door closes]
[tape rattles]
[footsteps thud on floorboards]
[floorboard creaks]
[door creaks open and shut]
[cables click]
[ominous music]
[camera chimes on]
[microphone static]
[video beeping on and off]
[David]: And action.
[Riley breathes nervously]
- Welcome back
to "Paranormal Para--."
[Mia laughs through tears]
Shit.
Um... Why did we choose
such a hard name?
[David]: You got it.
[Riley]: Okay, um...
welcome back
to the "Paranormal Paranoids."
Today we're taking
our first foray
into the mysterious world
of ghost towns.
Behind me rests the abandoned
town of Shelby Oaks,
located right on the edge
of Darke County, Ohio.
What really happened
to Shelby Oaks?
Some say the cops went bad,
so it went sour,
but truth is,
no one knows for sure.
That's why we're here.
[video beeps]
[Peter speaks indistinctly]
[unsettling music plays]
[David's footsteps crunch
approaching]
[David]: What is it?
[hesitates]
- I think...
I think we should leave.
[David]: What do you mean?
We just, we just got here.
[Laura]: Riley?
- Yeah,
but it doesn't feel right.
[sighs]
[Laura]: Riley.
You okay?
[Peter]: Riley, what's--
[David]: Are we seriously
gonna do this again?
[video beeps off]
[static crackles]
[David]: And action.
- Shelby Oaks Amusement Park.
In its heyday,
this was the only draw
for out-of-towners.
There was a ballroom,
a few rollercoasters,
even a hotel.
But after a series of
missing persons reports
and a devastating fire,
the park eventually
closed for good.
Now, all that remains of this
once joyful location
lies in these woods,
abandoned and forgotten.
[birds chirping]
[David]: Perfect.
First try, too.
- I think I had a dream
about this place.
[David chuckles]
[David]: Really?
- Yeah.
My mom used to come here
when she was little.
[David]: Hmm.
[blows out breath]
[knife rasps in bark]
[David]: "RM"?
- Yeah.
Mia will get it
when she sees it.
[laughs softly]
- Yeah.
[David]: Yeah, okay.
- Cool.
[Laura]: Should we get going?
[video glitches]
[heavy breathing]
[David]: I can't tell
if there's anyone there.
[Peter]: Yeah, man.
[David]: I don't think
there's anyone in there.
[Peter]: No.
[David]: Why don't you go back
around and check it out?
[Peter]: Yeah.
[David]: All right.
[video glitches]
[floorboards creaking]
[Laura]: Be careful.
[David]: Yeah.
[tapping]
[Peter]: Shit.
Shit. Shit.
Goddamn it.
[Laura]: We should sneak
out the back.
[Peter]: Listen, I'm not going
to jail over a video.
[David]: Hold on, hold
on, hold on.
[Peter]: What's he doing?
[David]: I don't know.
[Peter]: He's just fucking
standing there.
[Mia breathes shakily]
[Peter]: Do not walk.
[indistinct]
David, what the hell
are you doing?
[Laura]: What are you doing?
[birds chirping]
[David]: Whoa.
[breathes nervously]
[David]: Jesus.
Fuck, you scared
the shit out of me.
[chuckles nervously]
What? What?
Riley...
[Laura]: Riley?
[David]: Riley.
[door slams shut]
[David]: Wow, okay.
[video beeps off]
[coyotes howling in distance]
[footsteps tapping]
[video beeps]
[coyotes howling loudly]
[Peter]: David, look, um...
look, I-I didn't wanna say this
around the girls, man,
but I'm really freaked
out right now.
I mean, how the fuck are you
sleeping through this?
These sounds are coming
from everywhere. I mean,
they're, they're surrounding
the whole fucking place
right now.
I mean, listen to this shit,
man.
Can you fucking hear this shit?
How the fuck--
[video beeps off]
[video beeps on]
[Peter]: Come on,
I can't do this anymore.
[David]: Come on, guys.
- David.
[David]: We're getting
good stuff!
[loud bang]
[Mia breathes shakily]
[Peter]: Jesus Christ.
Get back, David.
[David]: Guys, get behind,
get behind.
[Peter]: God dammit, David--
[David]: Shh!
[door creaks open]
[crickets chirping]
[crickets chirping stops]
[slow footsteps thud
on floorboards]
[startling beat]
[Mia breathes nervously]
[man grunting]
[David groans loudly]
[squelching]
[shaky gasps]
[Peter]: Stop!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[sinister music swells]
[male breathing heavily]
[wind howling]
[male breathing quickens]
[sobbing]
[sinister music]
[Riley]: Help!
[breathing shakily]
[video glitches then snaps off]
[gasps]
[window cracks]
[door crashes open]
[Mia panting]
[door opens]
[Robert]: Honey?
What is it.
[panting continues]
- There's something
you need to see.
[video playing]
[heavy breathing]
[Riley]: Help!
[video ends]
[footsteps thud,
approaching slowly]
- How?
- It was in his hand.
- He brought it here?
Why didn't you give it
to the police?
- I needed to see it
for myself first.
- Come on.
C'mere.
[Burke]: The man's name
is Wilson Miles.
Born in Shelby Oaks in 1981.
He spent five years
at the old Darke County
Correctional
for aggravated assault
and battery.
- The prison Riley filmed at?
[Burke]: After he gets out,
he falls off the map.
No bills, phone records.
Odds are he found a hole
to hide in.
Until recently.
I know this is a...
delicate subject,
but do you have any reason
to believe that this
might have something
to do with your sister?
[Robert]: What's wrong with you?
You're withholding evidence now?
This is what you've been
searching for,
and now that you've got it,
you're keeping it to yourself?
- You think that tape
is what I've been searching for?
- That's...
that's not what I meant.
- What did the tape
actually tell us?
- That we know who
the killer is.
- And where is he now?
They'll use that tape as an
ending to the story.
They don't even have
to look for the guy.
His body's at the morgue, rotting.
What else is left for them?
- Riley.
- They already gave up on her!
For the cops,
this'll be nothing new.
Nothing will change.
And as soon as the public gets
a hold of it,
they'll drag Riley
through the dirt,
all over again.
It'll never fucking end.
Unless we find her first.
All I'm asking for
is a few days.
[tense energetic music]
I need this.
[keys clacking]
[pencil scratching]
[microfilm reel clunks]
[mouse clicking]
[microfilm reel whirs]
[keys clacking]
[demonic music plays briefly]
[Morton]: My prison died the day
that Wilson Miles arrived.
- How long were you
the warden there?
- Too long.
- In the interview I read,
you said that you
couldn't explain
the rapid deterioration
of the prison.
- I've had many years to think
about it since then.
But one member in particular
puts it all in perspective.
It was the day
of that awful riot.
A computer error unlocked
every cell in block three,
the last place you want
something like that to happen.
We used to call block three
the grave,
because all the folk there
had one foot in it.
- That's awful.
- What I saw in cell 37 was,
that was cell
of one Wilson Miles.
He was a peculiar man.
Very quiet.
Spoke to no one.
On that day...
[chilling beat]
[alarm wails]
[Morton]: His door was wide
open.
He could have tried to run.
But he just...
he just stood there.
Staring out the window.
Totally unaware of all
of the chaos surrounding him.
When the dust settled...
[chuckles]
there he remained.
That man was carrying something.
I don't know what it was...
but it left nothing
but death and rot
in my prison.
[exhales]
Are you sure he's dead?
- Very.
- Good.
[Riley]: Now all that remains
of this once joyful location
lies in these woods,
abandoned and forgotten.
I think I had a dream
about this place.
[chuckles]
[David]: Really?
- Yeah. My mom used to come here
when she was little.
[David]: "RM"?
[Riley]: Yeah.
Mia will get it when
she sees it.
[chuckles lovingly]
Yeah.
[overlapping chatter]
[David]: Cool.
[Laura]: Should we get going?
[video beeps]
[camera rewinds, whirring]
[David]: "RM"?
[Riley]: Yeah.
Mia will get it when
she sees it.
[chuckles lovingly]
Yeah.
[Mia]: Oh, my God.
[David]: Cool.
[button beeps]
[Mia breathes shakily]
[Mia]: Fair warning,
this kinda thing was more
Riley's ballpark,
but just hear me out.
1981, Wilson Miles is born
in Shelby Oaks,
almost immediately after
the town starts
losing residents.
Businesses close, crops fail,
the town barely survives
by hanging on to its one
and only draw...
the amusement park.
Riley and I went there
all the time.
By the Millennium,
there are two things left
in Shelby Oaks,
the amusement park,
and Darke County Correctional.
That was taken in 2002.
This is 2007.
After Wilson Miles
was there for five years.
- What does this have
to do with Riley?
- Her night terrors.
When she turns 13,
she stops having them.
- Yeah, but she grew
out of them.
- When Riley turns 13,
Wilson started his time
at Darke County.
Five years later,
he gets out, Riley disappears.
She didn't grow out of anything.
It was real.
- So, you think Wilson
was looking through
Riley's second story window?
- No.
[hesitates]
I'm gonna tell you something
I haven't told anyone.
Because up until now,
I wrote it off
as a false memory,
a bad dream.
[Mia]: When Riley was 9,
maybe 10,
she was having a rough week.
Every single night,
she was screaming, crying.
So, one night I decided
I'd sleep in the room with her.
I thought it might help.
And it did.
She slept through
the whole night.
But I didn't.
Not long after she fell asleep,
I heard something outside
the window,
scratching at the glass.
I turned over in bed,
I looked across the room...
and I saw it.
[glass cracks sharply]
I never told Mom or Riley.
After that,
I never saw it again.
[picture crinkles]
[eerie music]
Until now.
I think this thing used Wilson,
possessed him, controlled him,
whatever you wanna call it,
to get what its wanted
ever since it first
looked through her window.
[eerie music plays]
I know. I know it's...
I'm totally fucking nuts.
- Where did the years ago.
Hmm?
You need help, Mia.
[inhales shakily]
[footsteps thud away]
[front door opens
and slams shut]
[pictures rustling]
[disturbing music
building slowly]
[eerie beat]
[eerie music]
[windchime chimes gently]
[wind gusting]
[creature breathing creepily]
[creature breathing]
[unintelligible
satanic whisperings]
[breathing intensifies]
[disturbing music peaks
then fades]
[windchime chimes gently]
[Riley]: The Darke
County Correctional
would send shivers down
the spine of even
the most experienced
paranormal investigators.
Riots, murders,
alleged hauntings.
[footsteps echoing slowly]
- Jesus.
[David]: What?
- Don't you feel that?
- Feel what?
- Cold.
[video stops]
[footsteps echo]
[Morton]: That was
the cell of one...
Wilson Miles.
[ominous music plays]
[car roars past]
[glass shatters]
[music swells then fades]
[footsteps echoing]
[sinister music swells
then fades]
[nervous breathing]
[unsettling music builds]
[footsteps echoing]
[breathing shakily]
[sinister beat]
[heavy breathing]
[sinister music]
[unintelligible demonic speech]
[loud crash]
[shaky breathing echoes]
[light fizzles out]
[flashlight clatters]
[strange thump]
[thumps continue]
[creature growls loudly]
[arm whooshes]
[Mia screams]
[intense chase music]
[truck starts]
[engine revs]
[music continues]
[truck rumbles to a stop]
[gear shifter clunks]
[truck rumbles away]
[engine cuts off]
[flashlight clicks on]
[insects chirping]
[birds cawing]
[breathes shakily]
[hand rasps on bark]
[gentle sobbing]
[strange growl in distance]
[bird cawing]
[disconcerting swell]
[shaky breathing]
[shrill beat]
[gasps]
[growling intensifies]
[footsteps crunch softly]
[low ominous music rumbles]
[leaves rustling]
[ominous music fades]
[old woman]: May I help you?
- Sorry, I...
I didn't know anyone lived out
here anymore.
[old woman]: Oh, I have been out
since well...
before I can remember.
[clears throat]
Which isn't very far.
- Do you have a dog?
I followed one out here.
- A dog?
Oh... he's probably around
here somewhere.
Thinking he can get
a midnight snack.
[laughs creepily]
[strained inhale]
[old woman chuckles]
- I'm Mia.
- Mia. I'm Norma.
Won't you come inside?
[door creaks open]
[groans]
You can shut the door.
[door shuts]
[Norma grunts]
- Cracker?
- No, thank you.
- Hmm.
[Norma grumbles under breath]
- Maybe you can tell me
if you've seen this girl before?
- Melanie, is it?
- Mia.
This girl, have you seen her?
- Oh, I... I can't say
that I have.
[floorboard creaks upstairs]
[footsteps thud softly]
- You live alone out here,
Norma?
- Nope.
[Norma grumbles unintelligibly]
[grumbling continues]
[floorboards creaking]
[Norma]: What's the story
about that girl?
- She's my sister.
- Oh.
Tell me about her.
Oh, come on.
Entertain an old lady.
I haven't seen anybody
but my son
in I don't know how long.
- Is that who you live with,
your son?
- Mm-hmm.
Right behind you.
[ominous music plays]
[floorboard creaks]
[Norma:] Do you
have any children, Mia?
- No.
[Norma]: Oh.
Sorry.
Is there any, any reason?
- Just...
couldn't find the time.
- Hmm. I see.
[chuckles]
You sure there's nothing
more to the story?
[Mia]: Excuse me?
- Well, it's life, isn't it?
It's always about the timing.
Sometimes it gives,
sometimes it takes.
[floorboards creak]
Would you still want one?
- You know, come to think of it,
I am actually kinda hungry.
I think I might take you
up on that snack.
- Of course, my dear.
[groans]
[mumbles unintelligibly]
[pages rustle]
[eerie music plays]
[music intensifies]
[thunderous demonic music]
[music softens]
[Norma]: You should
be proud of her.
She was strong.
Just as I was.
She's been given the chance
to touch greatness.
- Where is she?
The police are on their way.
- That will make no difference.
- Tell me where she is,
right fucking now!
[floorboards creaking]
[Norma grumbling]
[lock clangs]
[hatch creaks open]
[Mia breathing shakily]
[Norma]: Don't be afraid.
It's a gift.
[floorboards creaking]
[purse unzips]
[breathing shakily]
[sinister music swells]
[Mia gasping loudly]
[unintelligible
demonic whisperings]
[knife clangs to floor]
- Riley?
[sobbing]
Honey, it's Mia.
Come to me.
I'm here, Riley.
I'm here.
[crack from behind]
[gasps]
Please, baby, hear me.
Riley.
I know you're in there.
[breathing shakily]
I found you.
[shaky exhale]
We're going home.
[keys jingling]
[lock clunks open]
[gate creaks]
- Okay, honey, come on.
Come on, honey.
Just a little farther.
[eerie music swelling]
Jesus Christ.
[thunderous music plays]
[hatch slams shut]
[clasp clangs]
[Mia panting]
Hurry. Hurry.
[Riley]: No. No! No!
- Riley.
[Riley sobbing]
Riley!
[ominous beat]
Fuck!
[unsettling music plays]
[Mia]: Riley?
Riley, honey...
[baby crying in distance]
[Mia breathing nervously]
[door creaks slowly]
[baby crying]
[blood dripping]
[crying continues]
[Norma]: Almighty Tarion,
Incubus of the North,
shield this Cambion!
[hateful scream]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[dramatic music plays]
[unintelligible
demonic whispers]
[Riley thuds to floor]
Almighty Tarion!
[baby cries]
Incubus of the North!
Shield this Cambion.
Bless him with the knowledge
of your all-seeing eyes.
[shrill beat]
Let Hell's hounds guard
his every move.
Bestow upon him your protection.
Let his seed be sown throughout
the land in your name!
Guide him to the fire!
[creature growling]
[demonic music building]
[music quiets]
[Norma whimpers]
[Norma groans]
[disturbing music plays]
[Norma grunts]
[blood squelches]
[unintelligible
demonic whisperings]
[breathes shakily]
[Norma exhales]
[gasping]
[exhales shakily]
[floorboards creak under foot]
[whimpering]
[baby cooing]
[sobs softly]
- Hi.
[sniffles]
[somber music plays]
[distant phone rings]
[baby babbling]
[babbling]
- Riley Brennan,
the long-lost host
of the now almost mythical
program "Paranormal Paranoids"
has been found alive.
She was discovered locked
in the basement of a house
in Shelby Oaks,
the ghost town on the edge
of Darke County, Ohio.
- The Darke County Police
Department has confirmed
they have, in their possession,
recently uncovered footage.
Coming up next, we'll be airing
the shocking tape that features
the final moments
of Peter Bailey,
Laura Tucker,
and David Reynolds,
as well as the abduction
of Riley Brennan.
We must warn you
that the footage
is extremely disturbing.
- Things are definitely
gonna be different.
I'm not sure there is a way
to go back to normal
after everything
we've been through.
I'm just grateful
to have her back.
[camera woman]: And...
we are rolling.
- Okay.
[camera woman]: Have you seen
any improvement in Riley
since bringing her home?
- Well, it's just the first day.
But she showed some signs
of awareness.
We still have a long road
ahead of us.
[camera woman]: How is Robert
adjusting to all this?
- He's taking some time
and we both think
that's healthy right now.
[camera woman]: And the baby?
[laughs happily]
- He's wonderful.
[chuckles]
There was some reluctance
at first,
given then circumstances.
But he'll be safe here.
[chuckles happily]
[baby coos]
[footsteps thud away]
[dark, unsettling music builds]
[trunk thuds shut]
- How's it coming along so far?
- Well, we've almost
finished editing
everything we shot before...
you know.
- Right.
- But, uh, this will make
a great ending to the story.
[door shuts]
[car starts]
[unsettling music crescendos]
[camera woman]: Hey,
one last thing,
you told the police you just
happened across that house.
Off the record...
[scoffs]
how did you really find her?
- I guess something
wanted me to.
[unsettling music continues]
[music stops abruptly]
[Mia]: Riley?
[wind howling]
[wild dogs barking]
[sobbing]
- It has to die.
- Honey...
think about what you're doing.
- You don't know
what's inside of him.
- I know my sister's not
a murderer.
Please...
back away.
[disturbing music builds]
- I love you, Mia.
- No!
[Mia and Riley grunting]
[window shatters]
[Riley thuds to ground]
[Mia]: Riley!
[heavy breathing]
[creature howling]
[creature growling wildly]
[creature growling]
[flesh squelching]
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[flesh ripping]
[sinister music plays]
[Mia]: I think this thing
used Wilson.
[window cracks sharply]
Possessed him, controlled him,
whatever you want to call it,
to get what it's wanted,
ever since it first looked
through her window.
[somber music plays]
[terrified shriek]
[thunderous ominous music]
Subtitling: difuze
♪ Oooh
♪ I am haunted in the morning
♪ I see a ghost
no one else does ♪
♪ I am haunted in the evening
♪ I see a ghost
where someone was ♪
♪ I can't see
where I'm going to ♪
and I'm falling ♪
♪ I can't see looking for you
♪ Come find me
I'm waiting for you ♪
♪ Oooh
♪ Big sister
I'm haunted in the morning ♪
are you coming for me? ♪
♪ Big sister
I'm haunted in the evening ♪
should I keep on waiting ♪
♪ Should I keep on waiting
♪ I think we might all ghosts
♪ I think we might
all be ghosts ♪
[woman]: You worry
your pretty little head.
There's nothing hiding
under your bed.
Dry those tears and try
to smile.
The sun will be up in just
a little while.
Go back to sleep,
there's no need to feel blue.
Your big sister
won't abandon you.